Sensei, it's time for class.
Yasuda-sensei.
Don't say I didn't try to wake you up.
Uh-oh, we should get back to the classroom.
The bell's about to ring.
Whoa. Yasuda's asleep.
His hair is so soft!
This'll look great.
Yasuda-sensei.
Yasuda-sensei!
Was there someone behind me just now?!
Yup, just a couple of third-years.
I bet they were girls!
How could I miss my chance like that?!
You know...
Damn, my class is already starting.
You know, Yasuda-sensei...
What is it?!
There's something wrong with your head.
I know that!
Why bring it up now?! I'm in a hurry!
I won't argue, but that's not what I meant.
I'm going to class!
Teacher
Your average on the last exams
was lower than the other classes'.
Write down an answer even if you're unsure.
You left way too many questions blank.
You're throwing points away.
Are you taking this seriously?
Yasuda, I...
What?
Do it!
Ask him, Hori-san!
Never mind.
Your English score was good, as usual.
Oh, um... Thanks.
What do I say?
I can't think of anything.
Does that bother you?
No, sir.
Excuse me!
What is it? Need to use the restroom?
Um, no...
Ask him, Miyamura!
You can do it, Miyamura-kun!
The theme...
Th-The theme?
The theme for today...
What about it?
Does that have anything
to do with what we're discussing?
Er, no. It doesn't, but...
No?
Then sit down.
Okay...
What's going on?
You all seem distracted by something.
It's you!
Oh, no! I overslept, and now I'm late!
What class are we on now?
I'm sorry for being late!
So you finally made it, Yoshikawa.
What gives, Yasuda?
You gotta stop! I can't!
I can't hold it back anymore!
Lookin' cute today, Yasuda!
What's gotten into you all?
I look cute?
Have a look, Yasuda.
What is this?!
How did you not notice?
You can't fool us!
Honestly...
If they're going to do that,
I want it done while I'm awake!
I want to be able to enjoy
teenage girls playing with my hair!
There really is something
wrong with his head.
That was a rare opportunity to...
Reference Room
Science Room
Library
Terajima-sensei, do you know
where the resource room key is?
I don't. Try asking the one
who's in charge of it.
And who would that be?
Nakamine-sensei, I believe.
Come to think of it, I think
he used the room yesterday.
Nakamine-sensei!
Please return the resource room key.
I put it back yesterday.
It isn't there.
But I put it back.
It's not there.
That's odd...
Oh.
Oh, it was in my pocket.
My bad.
Why is he in charge of the key?
Man, I'm glad we found it.
You just dropped a different key.
My bicycle key!
I thought I lost it over the summer.
O-Over the summer?
It's winter!
Thank you.
Now I can start riding my bike again.
I didn't really do anything...
No need to be humble.
Maybe we should entrust
the key to someone else.
Do you have any other keys on you?
I wonder...
Hey, it's Yasuda.
Who's that other teacher?
Nakamine-sensei.
Remember? The physics teacher.
Whoa!
How does your pocket do that?
Was that a magic trick?
That's a lot of keys!
Huh? Oh, thanks.
I could do that too if I tried!
You don't need to get
competitive about it, Yasuda.
No, I'm serious! I could totally do that!
Sensei, there was another key over here.
Oh, thank you. I would've been
in trouble again without that.
Huh?
Th-The resource room key is gone.
Nakamine-sensei!
Loop
Sensei!
You dropped these.
Oh, silly me.
Thank you.
Sensei, you might have a hole in your pocket.
What? There's no way...
Sensei, I have a sewing kit.
You don't say!
Home Economics
You're quite skilled with
your hands, young lady.
Sensei, I'm Yoshikawa from class 3-1.
R-Right...
Sorry.
I don't teach class 3-1.
But you taught us as first-years.
Did you forget?
I've had trouble remembering
faces and names since I was young.
But I remember you.
It's an affair.
But it's Nakamine-sensei...
But it's Nakamine-sensei!
How'd he do it?
How'd he get a teenage girl alone
doing that for him?
Shut up. How should I know? Drop dead.
I don't like hearing
you say that so casually.
This is no time to start
acting like a real teacher!
Gotta say, I never expected
Yoshikawa to carry a sewing set.
I had no idea either. What's more...
Toru, you're missing a button.
Oh, I didn't notice.
Honestly. Make sure you sew it back on.
That's how she treated me this summer!
Sounds like she has
no love for you whatsoever.
You might as well be "Rando A" to her.
Don't talk like you know how she feels
when you don't, you sexual harasser!
Then what about Nakamine-sensei?
What about him, huh?!
Nakamine doesn't give off even a whiff of
ulterior motives, criminality, or indecency.
You, on the other hand...
What?! I have only the purest intentions!
Huh?!
Wow!
You sewed it right up. Thank you so much.
Let me know if you ever get another hole.
And take better care of those keys!
Yoshikawa-san, do you always
have a needle and thread on you?
Yeah, sure do.
There's a certain someone
who keeps losing his buttons.
But he doesn't tell me when it happens.
Oh, that's really too bad.
Say, to show my appreciation,
can I get you something to drink?
No, thanks. I'm still working on this.
Hey, instead, Sensei,
let me see your hand.
What are they talking about?
How should I know?
She finished mending...
Toru?
Oh my.
What were you doing back there?
What do you mean?
With his hands.
Oh, that?
I was doing a palm reading.
What brought that on?
I'm into it lately. It's neat.
I can read yours, too!
Nah, I'll pass.
It's fine. I don't mind.
Your palm lines are so faint!
Just like Nakamine-sensei's!
That's what you were looking at?!
Aren't you supposed to tell me how lucky I am?
I can't tell that.
Go watch your horoscope on the news.
Talk about a total cop out.
Listen, have you read anyone else's palms?
Nope.
Oh, I did look at Hori's.
Her lines were really easy to see.
Why do you ask?
I just don't want anyone
thinking you're a weirdo.
Not that I do.
Wait, are you saying you think I'm weird?!
No!
I'm not a weirdo! I'm not!
I know.
Ishikawa!
Miyamura says he's in for tomorrow!
Nice! Where should we go, then?
What if we go find an empty classroom, bro?
Who are calling "bro"?
Ooh, what's this? Lemme in on it!
Just a little guy fun!
Sounds dumb.
What?!
I had a hard time sneaking this in here.
Talk about huge...
We all know bigger is better.
Student Council
I think looks are important, too.
No way. Size is where the romance lies.
Hello, young adolescent boys!
What do we have here
that's got you all so... excited...
Where do you live, Yasuda?
Why? Are you going to come
burn my place down?
No, I'm just interested.
You don't need to be interested
in where your teachers live.
Student Counseling
And besides, you three are in trouble.
Do you get that?
Sorry.
But school policy doesn't
forbid having cake in a classroom.
A whole cake is just too much.
Come to think of it, you live
pretty close to school, right?
I remember sending you a New Year's card.
Are you planning to visit?!
You'd better not! And we're
still talking about the cake!
We don't care about the cake anymore.
We want to know how you live.
You're a little too honest.
Do you live by yourself?
Huh? Well, you could say that...
Got a girlfriend?
No.
Why does that matter anyway?
Because, you know...
You always go around saying how
much you like high school girls.
If you had a perfectly normal,
uninteresting girlfriend...
Perfectly normal girlfriend
Yasuda's perfectly
normal girlfriend (pending)
I'd be disappointed.
"Uninteresting"?
Ah, yeah, I get that.
If he had a girlfriend,
that alone would be a shock.
Right?
I said I don't, so you're safe.
Yasuda, let me know if you ever get a
perfectly normal and uninteresting girlfriend.
Perfectly normal girlfriend
Yasuda's perfectly
normal girlfriend (pending)
Has no hobbies
What exactly are you going for here?
Don't you want to get married?
I don't have anyone to marry.
Weren't you listening?
You should do it.
Marry your super-normal,
completely uninteresting girlfriend.
Perfectly normal girlfriend
Yasuda's perfectly
normal girlfriend (pending)
Has no hobbies
Her friends are all getting
married recently
Seriously, who the hell are you talking about?
I mean, I just don't want Nakamine-sensei
to get married before I do.
He's really fixated on Nakamine.
Damn it, I'm fraternizing with students!
I'd love to see where you live.
Yeah!
You jerks aren't welcome!
However, if you bring some girls,
I'll allow you in!
Miyamura, you bring Hori!
Ishikawa, you bring Yoshikawa!
Iura, you bring Ayasaki and Kono!
Huh?
Then forget it.
Hey, what happened to your enthusiasm?
I wanna see where you live!
You're the worst.
I'm not sending you
a New Year's card next year.
I wasn't expecting one.
I don't know what you're thinking,
but those two don't have any
strong feelings toward me!
Oh, I see.
Sorry.
Now, back to the cake...
Forget it.
Go back to class.
Oh, can we? Yay!
Student Counseling
Yasuda, we'll come visit again.
Sure, just bring me some cake, too.
What a terrible teacher.
Sensei, we'll come back
for the cake after school,
so be sure to keep it cold.
I know.
Just what is this?
Science Prep Room
It's nine o'clock
in the student council room.
The door's locked...
and there's a slumbering demon.
How could she fall asleep?
Is it drugs?
Is she taking drugs?!
It's because
the room's so warm
A-Anyway, I'll let the demon sleep.
If I call the school, it should
ring in the faculty office.
Please Charge
Why?!
Whoa, it's dark.
What's going on? What time is it?
I'm done for.
It seems...
someone locked the door
while we were sleeping.
How could you let that happen, you idiot?!
Y-You didn't wake up either, Kyo-chan!
Don't put all the blame on me!
Aw, man! I was going to
buy carrots on the way home!
What am I supposed to do now?!
The gardening club's growing
a bunch. Just take those.
What kind of council president are you?!
Kyo-chan, your phone! Call someone!
The school! Anyone! Just do it!
Is that how you ask someone to do something?
No, I'm sorry.
But please hurry.
Okay, fine.
Sengoku, what's the school's phone number?
You should have that stored!
Can it.
We just need to check the student handbook.
Right! Now hurry up and call! Make it snappy!
Why are you in such a rush?
You don't need to use the restroom, do you?
Don't copy me.
It's perfectly natural!
Wait, you have to go, too?!
Honestly, what the hell are you two doing?
I was just going home—
Hey, where are you going?!
Where's my thank you?!
Restroom
Student Counseling
So, what were you doing here so late?
He fell asleep.
Hang on. Hori-san was asleep, too.
Are you serious?
You weren't up to something
inappropriate, were you?
Huh?
What do you mean?
It happens. Students stay
late and start making out.
Hold it! Don't accuse us of that!
And isn't this the fault of whoever locked
the door without checking inside first?
Hmm? What was that?
I can't hear you.
Well, there are ways
to figure out what you were up to.
Hori, take off your clothes!
What's going on here, Yasuda-sensei?
Terajima-sensei, you're just in time.
You check Sengoku.
It would be the other way around.
And I'm not checking anyone.
This is ridiculous.
Checking their lower bodies
will tell us everything.
We won't be doing that.
I certainly hope you haven't used that excuse
to do anything inappropriate
to female students.
You two may go home.
I need to speak with this perv of a teacher.
Okay!
Terajima-sensei, calling me
a perv is going too far!
Student Counseling
If you'll excuse us...
Wait, stop!
Now, we're going to go over this in detail.
I need to hurry home.
It's so cold in the hallway.
Huh? You got locked in, Hori-san?
Are you okay?
You could have just called me.
No need. We got out pretty quickly.
Were you alone?
Weren't you scared?
I wasn't alone. Sengoku was there.
President, are you okay?
You were stuck in a room
with Hori-san, right?
Did she doing anything to you?
I'm fine. Safe and sound.
Hey.
What do you mean by that?
I-I mean, just considering
the power dynamic...
Right?!
Leave me out of this, Miyamura-kun!
I'd like to hear exactly what you mean.
This is what he's talking about, Kyo-chan!
Huh?
Hori-san, you mustn't resort to violence.
Consider anger a chance to improve yourself,
and purge it from your body.
That was Yasuda, right?
It certainly looked like him.
It sounds like he got a talking-to from
Terajima-sensei and had a change of heart.
That was more than a change of heart!
More like he's been brainwashed.
Terajima-sensei is amazing!
Huh?
Life is precious.
He was back to normal
the next day
Next time
page.10 Jealousy